Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/dwiky-aprian-ashari-697082148 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Kotlin

Android

Web Development

Languages

English (Elementary)
Indonesian (Native or Bilingual)
Javanese (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Cloud Practitioner Essentials (Belajar Dasar AWS Cloud)

Belajar Prinsip Pemrograman SOLID

Belajar Machine Learning untuk Pemula

Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Android untuk Pemula

Honors-Awards

1st Place of Programming
- Kompetisi Mahasiswa
Muhammadiyah (KMM) 2020

Lomba Inovasi Digital Mahasiswa 2020 Finalist

Top 10% Distinction Graduates Bangkit 2021

Lomba Inovasi Digital Mahasiswa 2021 Finalist

1st Place of Programming
- Kompetisi Mahasiswa
Muhammadiyah (KMM) 2021

Dwiky Aprian Ashari

Software Engineer at Tokopedia

Banyuwangi

Summary

Experienced in Software Engineering, especially in Backend and Native Android Apps. Now I am prefer to develop with Kotlin & Go as my programming language. I am currently continuing my 7th semester of Informatics majoring at the University of Muhammadiyah Malang and have a passion for development and technology such as coding, research, and competitive programming.

Experience

Tokopedia

7 months

Software Engineer June 2022 - Present (1 month) Jakarta, Indonesia

Software Engineer Intern December 2021 - June 2022 (7 months)

Jakarta, Indonesia

Google Developer Student Clubs UMM Core Team

September 2021 - June 2022 (10 months)

Malang, East Java, Indonesia

Informatics Laboratory UMM

2 years 10 months

Laboratory Assistant

August 2019 - May 2022 (2 years 10 months)

Malang, East Java, Indonesia

Full Stack Engineer

August 2020 - January 2022 (1 year 6 months)

Malang, East Java, Indonesia

Alterra Academy
Full Stack Engineering Student
August 2021 - January 2022 (6 months)

Malang, East Java, Indonesia

Part of Studi Independent Merdeka Belajar Kampus Merdeka

SmartLBM
Full Stack Engineer
December 2020 - November 2021 (1 year)
Sragen Regency, Central Java, Indonesia

Sekawan Media Software Engineer Intern July 2021 - October 2021 (4 months) Malang, East Java, Indonesia

PT Asuransi Tugu Pratama Indonesia Tbk Software Engineer Intern August 2021 - September 2021 (2 months) Jakarta, Indonesia

Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, & Traveloka Mobile Programming Student led by Google February 2021 - July 2021 (6 months)

CV. Pendekar Internet Marketing SEO Engineer Intern February 2016 - April 2016 (3 months) Banyuwangi, East Java, Indonesia

Education

University Of Muhammadiyah Malang Bachelor's degree, Informatics · (2018 - 2022)

SMK Muhammadiyah 8 Siliragung High School, Computer Software Engineering (2015 - 2018)